Lesson 21, Susan gets a surprise call.
Donna, from the National Cookie Company, calls Susan.
She wants to buy out Susan's scrumptious cookies.
Susan is very happy.
Hello, good afternoon.
Are you Susan of Susan's scrumptious cookies?
Yes I am.
My name is Donna Jenkins, and I'm calling from the National Cookie Company.
We're nuts about your cookies, and we'd like to sell them all over the country.
Unfortunately, we're running on a shoestring out of our kitchen.
We can't make enough cookies for you.
My company wants to buy the recipe and the brand name from you.
Oh yeah?
Why would you want to do that?
We have a successful track record of buying small companies,
and turning them into big ones.
In that case, I'm sure we can come to an agreement.
Great. You just made my day.
You'll need to work out the nuts and bolts of the agreement with my husband.
He's the business manager.
May I speak with him now?
He's at a meeting.
I'll have him get in touch with you when he returns.
Good. I look forward to speaking with him.